Guide to the Cullen College of Engineering Records
University of Houston Libraries
- Publications
  - MX maintenance management system definition, September 1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Theory of Cellwise Optimization for Solar central receiver systems, September 1981 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Applications of Heterogeneous Catalysis, May 10-14, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Graduate Studies, August 16, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Mechanical Engineering - Graduate Studies, August 31, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - International IEEE/APS Symposium & Nat. Radio Science meeting, May 23-26, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - National Radio Meeting, May 23-26, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Annual Research Summary, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - A study of the effects of scale, velocity, & cycle degradability, October 1984 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Chemical Engineering, Graduate Studies, November 29, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Annual Research Summary, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Triangulation Databases & Algorithms: W.M. Smith, April 1985 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Applications of Heterogeneous Catalysis, May 5-9, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Basic Research in Energy Engineering, August 15, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Report on workshop sponsored by National Science Foundation, March 2-4, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - The sixth U.S. National Conference on Wind Engineering, March 8-10, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Ninth Annual Conference on Biomedical Engineering Research, February 7-8, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Eleventh Annual Conference on Biomedical Engineering Research, February 11-12, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Twelfth Annual Conference on Biomedical Engineering Research, February 10-11, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Thirteenth Annual Conference on Biomedical Engineering Research, February 16-17, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Fourteenth Annual Conference on Biomedical Engineering Research, February 8-9, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Fifteenth Annual Conference on Biomedical Engineering Research, February 13-14, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Sixteenth Annual Conference on Biomedical Engineering Research, April 2-3, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Seventeenth Annual Conference on Biomedical Engineering Research, February 11-12, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Eighteenth Annual Conference on Biomedical Engineering Research, February 10-11, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Nineteenth Annual Conference on Biomedical Engineering Research, February 8-9, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - 25th Annual Conference on Biomedical Engineering Research, February 7-8, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 27)